CHRISTIAN BEAM

Contact

ckbbeamcoding@gmail.com

(941) 416-6424

54 6th St W Nokomis, FL, 34275

Links:

https://github.com/beamchristian Portfolio:

https://beamchristian.github.io/ LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/christianbeam-64b5b5a0

Career Summary

Dedicated and hard working MERN stack specialist with over 1 year of experience in multiple front and backend technologies. I have completed a Full-Stack Certification bootcamp through the University of Central Florida for Web Design. My previous experience in retail has given me an unbreakable work ethic and leadership ability that will carry me into my next career in technology.

Technical Skills

HTML5 React.js IndexedDb

CSS MySQL Handlebars.js

Bootstrap Sequelize Webpack

Bulma MongoDB GraphQI

Javascript(ES6+) Mongoose Apollo Client

Jest Express.js Express.js

Bcrypt.js Node.js Git

Experience

July 2021 - Present

DELI TEAM LEAD

Detwiler's Farm Market, Sarasota, FL

- Organizing team to maintain customer service on the service counter.
- Maintaining a regular cleaning schedule for equipment used on the service counter.
- Assisting with monthly inventory audits and training new hires on processes in the department.
- Provide great customer service.
- Assisting customers by providing product knowledge and resolving any questions or complaints.

May 2020 - June 2021

DELI MANAGER

Detwiler's Farm Market, Sarasota, FL

- Trained, coached, motivated and supervised 8 employee's in products, procedures, and customer service.
- Managed product storage and rotation to avoid damages and spoilage.
- Handled all customer issues in a gracious manner in accordance with company policies.
- Ensured that displays grabbed the customers attention as well as signage.
- Understanding of products and ability to be able to step into any position and assist customers. Led by example to ensure daily objectives are being met.
- Display a positive attitude; promote trust and respect among associates.

March 2018 - April 2020

ASSISTANT DELI MANAGER

Detwiler's Farm Market, Sarasota, FL

- Role model outstanding friendly customer service and use skills and knowledge to offer solutions that meet or exceed customers expectations.
- Slice deli meats, cheese and platters to customers request using proper deli equipment according to company guidelines.
- Submit orders according to product on hand and inventory needs.
- Assisted in employee reviews and coaching sessions.

DELI CLERK

Detwiler's Farm Market, Sarasota, FL

- Assisted customers on the service counter by delivering prompt and friendly service.
- Worked with cheese and meat slicers according to company safety standards and policies.
- Maintained production list throughout the day to ensure deli cases were fully stocked.
- Coordinating with other staff to maintain safety standards and cleaning procedures.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Orlando, FL Full Stack Coding Bootcamp Web Design (Feb 2022)

NORTH PORT HIGH SCHOOL

North Port, FL High School Diploma (May 2010)